A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation photographs FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Brazil - Yellow Fever
  - SEPFA Laboratory (Box 70, Folder 1515)
  - Connor (Box 70, Folder 1516)
  - Wilson, D. B. (Box 70, Folder 1517)
- Brazil - Humanities and Arts
  - University of Bahia - Drama School (Box 70, Folder 1518)
- Brazil - Virus Studies
  - Causey, O.R. (Box 70, Folder 1519)
  - Belem Virus Laboratory - Evandro Chagas Institute (Box 70, Folder 1520)
  - Belem Virus Laboratory and Special Public Health Service Foundation (Box 70, Folder 1521)
  - Administration - Belem Virus Laboratory (Box 70, Folder 1522)
- Chile
  - Agriculture (Box 70, Folder 1523)
    Agriculture, farming, indigenous peoples, laborers, houses, markets.
  - Agriculture - Catholic University Experiment Station (Box 70, Folder 1524)
    Agriculture, farming, corn, laboratories.
  - Agriculture - Chillan Experiment Station (Box 70, Folder 1525)
  - Agriculture - Experimental Projects (Box 70, Folder 1526)
    Agriculture, animals, farming, pigs.
  - Agriculture - Farinology Laboratory (Box 70, Folder 1527)
  - Administration - Farm Machinery (Box 70, Folder 1528)
    Agriculture, farming, equipment.
  - Agriculture - La Patina Experiment Station (Box 70, Folder 1529)
    Agriculture, farming, group portraits.
  - Agriculture - La Rinconda Experiment Station - Maipu and Santiago (Box 70, Folder 1530)
    Agriculture, farming, laboratories, field stations, corn, plants.
  - Agriculture - Osorno (Box 70, Folder 1531)
    Agriculture, farming, animals, cows.
  - Agriculture - Paine Experimental Station (Box 71, Folder 1532)
    Agriculture, farming, wheat.
  - Agriculture - Quinta Normal (Box 71, Folder 1533)
    Laboratories, plaques, buildings.
  - Agriculture - Santiago Experiment Station (Box 71, Folder 1534)
    Agriculture, experiment stations, farming, crops, machinery.
  - Agriculture - Temuco Experiment Station (Box 71, Folder 1535)
    Agriculture, experiment stations, farming, group portraits, crops, wheat, animals, cows.
  - Agriculture - United States Foreign Operations Administration and Chilean Ministry of Agriculture (Box 71, Folder 1536)
    Agriculture, farming, cattle.
  - Agriculture - University of Chile (Box 71, Folder 1537)
    Agriculture, farming, experiments, plant breeding, portraits.
  - Agriculture - University of Concepcion - School of Agronomy (Box 71, Folder 1538)
    Agriculture, farming, laboratories, libraries.
  - Insectary - La Cruz (Box 71, Folder 1539)
    Laboratories, insects.
  - Pearce - Reports on Pneumonia and on Welfare Work at the Mines of the Braden Copper Company, Rancagua, Chile (Box 71, Folder 1540)
    Villages, aerial views, houses, hotels, group portraits.
  - University of Concepcion - Album (Box 71, Folder 1541)
    Schools, cities, libraries, students, laboratories, families, landscapes.
  - University of Concepcion - Album (Box 72, Folder 1542)
  - General (Box 72, Folder 1543)
  - Univeristy of Chile (Box 72, Folder 1544)
    Schools, construction, models.
  - Agriculture - Entomology and Plant Genetics (Box 72, Folder 1545)
    Group portraits, laboratories.
  - Bacteriological Institute, Santiago - Virus Research (Box 72, Folder 1546)
    Motion picture equipment, laboratories.
  - Catholic University - Agronomy (Box 72, Folder 1547)
    Agriculture, farming, chickens, cows, crops, wheat.
  - University of Chile (Box 72, Folder 1548)
    Agriculture Experiment Station. Crop research. Genetics. Marine biology laboratory. Agriculture, farming, aerial views, farming equipment.
  - University of Concepcion - Agriculture (Box 72, Folder 1549)
    Agriculuture, farming, laboratories, schools, libraries.
  - Hospitals (Box 72, Folder 1550)
    Hospitals, exteriors, interiors, laboratories, group portraits.
  - Catholic University - Drama (Box 72, Folder 1551)
  - University of Chile - Economics (Box 72, Folder 1552)
    Schools, libraries.
  - University of Chile - Laboratory Pictures (Box 72, Folder 1553)
- Chile - Medical Sciences
  - General (Box 72, Folder 1543)
  - Univeristy of Chile (Box 72, Folder 1544)
- Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture
  - Agriculture - Entomology and Plant Genetics (Box 72, Folder 1545)
  - Bacteriological Institute, Santiago - Virus Research (Box 72, Folder 1546)
  - Catholic University - Agronomy (Box 72, Folder 1547)
  - University of Chile (Box 72, Folder 1548)
  - University of Concepcion - Agriculture (Box 72, Folder 1549)
- Chile - Hospital Administration
  - Hospitals (Box 72, Folder 1550)
- Chile - Humanities and Arts
  - Catholic University - Drama (Box 72, Folder 1551)
- Chile - Social Sciences
  - University of Chile - Economics (Box 72, Folder 1552)
- Chile - Virus Studies
  - University of Chile - Laboratory Pictures (Box 72, Folder 1553)
- Colombia
  - General (Box 72, Folder 1554)
    Colombia, agriculture, farming, landscapes.
  - Agriculture (Box 72, Folder 1555)
    Agriculture, conferences.
  - Agriculture - Views of Bogota (Box 72, Folder 1556)
    Citiescapes.
  - Agriculture - Cobb, William C. - Trip Photos (Box 72, Folder 1557)
    Colombia, trips.
  - Agriculture - General Agricultural Photos (Box 72, Folder 1558)
    Agriculture, farming, group portraits, laborers, equipment, plants, aerial views, wheat.
  - Agriculture - Colombian Agricultural Program Office of Special Investigations - 4th Annual Progress Report (Box 73, Folder 1559)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, wheat, corn, reports.
  - Agriculture - Colombian Agricultural Program Directors Report (Box 73, Folder 1560)
    Agriculture, farming, equipment, laborers, crops, corn.
  - Agriculture - Colombian Agricultural Program Directors Annual Report (Box 73, Folder 1561)
    Agriculture, corn, farming.
  - Agriculture - Colombian Agricultural Program Directors Annual Report (Box 73, Folder 1562)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, corn, wheat, specimens, laborers.
  - Agriculture - Colombian Minister of Agriculture - Visit (Box 73, Folder 1563)
    Agriculture, conferences, group portraits.
  - Agriculture - Conferences - Bogota, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1564)
  - Agriculture - Corn (Box 74, Folder 1565)
  - Agriculture - Lindsley F. Kimball Accepts for RF the Colombian Decoration Award (Box 74, Folder 1566)
    Award given in recognition of Rockefeller Foundation's help in developing agriculture programs. Agriculture, awards, ceremonies, group portraits.
  - Agriculture - Dia Exhibit - Agriculture Fair, Medellin (Box 74, Folder 1567)
    Agriculture, exhibits.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Medellin and Tulio Ospina (Box 74, Folder 1568)
    Agriculture, experiment stations, farming, buildings, conferences, crops, corn, schools, classrooms, libraries, laboratories.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Medellin and Tulio Ospina (Box 74, Folder 1569)
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Palmira (Box 75, Folder 1570)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, corn, laborers, field stations, buildings, equipment, animals.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Palmira (Box 75, Folder 1571)
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Tibaitata (Box 75, Folder 1572)
    Agriculture, field stations, farming, buildings, conferences, crops, corn.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Tibaitata (Box 75, Folder 1573)
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Tibaitata - Duplicates (Box 76, Folder 1574)
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Tibaitata (Box 76, Folder 1575)
    Agriculture, farming, animals, classrooms, landscapes, experiment stations, crops, wheat, animals, pigs, construction, conferences.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Tibaitata (Box 76, Folder 1576)
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Various (Box 76, Folder 1577)
    Aagriculture, farming, experiment stations, laboratories, crops, wheat, animals, buildings.
  - Agriculture - Fiftieth Anniversary Picture Book (Box 76, Folder 1578)
    Agriculture, farming, animals.
  - Agriculture - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Visit (Box 76, Folder 1579)
  - Agriculture - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Visit (Box 76, Folder 1580)
  - Agriculture - La Ceja (Box 76, Folder 1581)
    Agriculture, farming, landscapes.
  - Agriculture - Livestock (Box 76, Folder 1582)
    Agriculture, farming, animals, cattle.
  - Agriculture - Pests and Blights (Box 77, Folder 1583)
    Agriculture, farming, plants, diseases.
  - Agriculture - Rice (Box 77, Folder 1584)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, rice.
  - Agriculture - Wheat (Box 77, Folder 1585)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, wheat.
  - Agriculture - Administration - Rockefeller Foundation Staff House at Griahat (Box 77, Folder 1586)
    Agriculture, RF staff, houses.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Colombian Agricultural Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1587)
    Agriculture, farming, animals, cows, experiment stations, crops, wheat.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Colombian Agricultural Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1588)
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Colombian Agricultural Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1589)
    Agriculture, farming, experiment stations, crops, wheat, animals, cows.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1590)
    For Colombia, see pages 105-180. Agriculture, farming, experiment stations, animals, cows, sheep, pigs, chickens, crops, wheat, plants, diseases.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1591)
    For Colombia, see pages 105-191. Agriculture, farming, crops, animals.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 77, Folder 1592)
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1593)
    Colombian Agricultural Program. Agriculture, farming, animals, cows, sheep, crops, wheat.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1594)
    Agriculture, farming, animals, experiment stations, crops, laboratories.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1595)
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1596)
    Colombian Agricultural Program. Agriculture, farming, animals, cattle, sheep, laboratories.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1597)
    Colombian Agricultural Program. Agriculture, farming, experiment stations, animals, crops.
  - Agriculture - R. Annual - Agricultural Sciences Program Annual Report (Box 78, Folder 1598)
    Agriculture, experiment stations, farming, equipment, crops.
  - Animal Program (Box 78, Folder 1599)
    Agriculture, farming, cattle, landscapes.
  - Cali Medical School (Box 78, Folder 1600)
    Schools, floor plans.
  - Cali Medical School - Medical Entomology (Box 78, Folder 1601)
    Schools, entomology.
  - Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 1602)
    Geographical Institute of the Colombian Andes. La Mesa. Leprosy. Marsupials. National School of Hygiene. National School of Nursing. Palestina. Buildings, animals, monkeys, libraries, cityscapes.
  - Sawyer - Report on Trip to Colombia (Box 78, Folder 1603)
    Cities, celebrations, parades, towns, group portraits, villages, boats.
  - University of the Andes (Box 79, Folder 1604)
  - University of Antioquia - Library School (Box 79, Folder 1605)
    Schools, libraries, group portraits, students.
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 79, Folder 1606)
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 79, Folder 1607)
    Cities, towns, rainforests, rivers, landscapes, villages, children, schools, medical exams, conferences.
  - Universidad del Valle - Duplicates (Box 79, Folder 1608)
  - Universidad del Valle - Visit of John D. Rockefeller 3rd (Box 79, Folder 1609)
  - Universidad del Valle - Survey Team (Box 79, Folder 1610)
  - Cali Medical School (Box 79, Folder 1611)
    Group portraits, citiscenes, aerial views, plans, doctors, nurses, medical exams, children, families.
  - Cali Medical School - Candelaria Health Center (Box 79, Folder 1612)
    Public health, clinics, sanitation, families, children.
  - Cali Medical School - Faculty of Medicine - Kellogg Foundation Fellows (Box 79, Folder 1613)
  - Cali Medical School - Population (Box 79, Folder 1614)
    Families, census data collection.
  - National University of Colombia - Medical School at Cali - University Health Center Project (Box 79, Folder 1615)
    Schools, laboratories, classrooms, buildings.
  - University of the Andes - Cell Physiology (Box 79, Folder 1616)
    Schools, laboratories.
  - University of the Andes - Premedical Studies (Box 79, Folder 1617)
  - University of Caldas - Medical Library (Box 79, Folder 1618)
  - National University of Colombia - Nursing School (Box 80, Folder 1619)
  - School of Nursing, Bogata (Box 80, Folder 1620)
    Group portraits, buildings, laboratories, housing.
  - Universidad del Valle - Building (Box 80, Folder 1621)
  - Universidad del Valle - Nursing School (Box 80, Folder 1622)
    Schools, nursing, wards, patients, interviews.
  - Agricultural Education - Instituto Colombiano Agropecuario (Box 80, Folder 1623)
    Group portraits, conferences, speeches.
  - Agriculture - Potato Improvement - Tibaitata Experiment Station - Nixon Address (Box 80, Folder 1624)
    Agriculture, farming, conferences, speeches, President Richard M. Nixon.
  - Agriculture - Wheat Breeding Program (Box 80, Folder 1625)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, wheat, equipment.
  - National University of Colombia (Box 80, Folder 1626)
    Agricultural equipment and dormitories at Medellin and Palmira. Schools, buildings, construction.
  - National University of Colombia - Agriculture - Medellin (Box 80, Folder 1627)
    Schools, laboratories, classrooms, buildings, agriculture, group portraits.
  - National University of Colombia - Agriculture - Palmira (Box 80, Folder 1628)
    Agriculture, schools, buildings, construction, laboratories.
  - Palmira Experiment Station (Box 80, Folder 1629)
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 80, Folder 1630)
    Biology. Chemical engineering. Agriculture, schools, laboratories, classrooms.
  - Hospitals (Box 80, Folder 1631)
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1632)
    Diseases, children, families, offices, group portraits, street scenes.
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1633)
    Diseases, case studies, families, children, field laboratories, dispensaries, Rockefeller Foundation staff.
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1634)
    Diseases, case studies, group portraits, families, children, privies, sanitation, dispensaries.
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1635)
    Diseases, sanitation, privies, indigenous peoples, group portraits, children.
  - Malaria (Box 80, Folder 1636)
  - Public Health (Box 81, Folder 1637)
  - Sawyer - Public Health in Colombia (Box 81, Folder 1638)
    Cities, villages, buildings, houses, landscapes, parades, group portraits, fishing.
  - Health Services (Box 81, Folder 1639)
    Buildings, laboratories, animals, stables, equipment.
  - Health Services - Laboratorio Nacional de Samper-Martinez, Bogota (Box 81, Folder 1640)
    Buildings, laboratories, wards, examination rooms, farming, group portraits.
  - Yellow Fever (Box 81, Folder 1641)
    Diseases, field stations, animals, opposum, group portraits, laboratories.
  - Escuela Normal Superior; National Library of Bogota (Box 81, Folder 1642)
    Agriculture, farming, buildings, libraries.
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 81, Folder 1643)
    Architecture, English, Library, Music. Schools, language instruction, performing arts.
  - University of the Andes - Economic Research (Box 81, Folder 1644)
    Group portraits, children.
  - Cali Virus Program (Box 81, Folder 1645)
    Diseases, mosquitos, sample collection, villages, indigenous peoples.
- Colombia - Medical Sciences
  - Cali Medical School (Box 79, Folder 1611)
  - Cali Medical School - Candelaria Health Center (Box 79, Folder 1612)
  - Cali Medical School - Faculty of Medicine - Kellogg Foundation Fellows (Box 79, Folder 1613)
  - Cali Medical School - Population (Box 79, Folder 1614)
  - National University of Colombia - Medical School at Cali - University Health Center Project (Box 79, Folder 1615)
  - University of the Andes - Cell Physiology (Box 79, Folder 1616)
  - University of the Andes - Premedical Studies (Box 79, Folder 1617)
  - University of Caldas - Medical Library (Box 79, Folder 1618)
- Colombia - Nursing
  - National University of Colombia - Nursing School (Box 80, Folder 1619)
  - School of Nursing, Bogata (Box 80, Folder 1620)
  - Universidad del Valle - Building (Box 80, Folder 1621)
  - Universidad del Valle - Nursing School (Box 80, Folder 1622)
- Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture
  - Agricultural Education - Instituto Colombiano Agropecuario (Box 80, Folder 1623)
  - Agriculture - Potato Improvement - Tibaitata Experiment Station - Nixon Address (Box 80, Folder 1624)
  - Agriculture - Wheat Breeding Program (Box 80, Folder 1625)
  - National University of Colombia (Box 80, Folder 1626)
  - National University of Colombia - Agriculture - Medellin (Box 80, Folder 1627)
  - National University of Colombia - Agriculture - Palmira (Box 80, Folder 1628)
  - Palmira Experiment Station (Box 80, Folder 1629)
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 80, Folder 1630)
- Colombia - Hospital Administration
  - Hospitals (Box 80, Folder 1631)
- Colombia - Hookworm
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1632)
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1633)
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1634)
  - Hookworm (Box 80, Folder 1635)
- Colombia - Malaria
  - Malaria (Box 80, Folder 1636)
- Colombia - Public Health Demonstrations
  - Public Health (Box 81, Folder 1637)
  - Sawyer - Public Health in Colombia (Box 81, Folder 1638)
- Colombia - Health Services
  - Health Services (Box 81, Folder 1639)
  - Health Services - Laboratorio Nacional de Samper-Martinez, Bogota (Box 81, Folder 1640)
- Colombia - Yellow Fever
  - Yellow Fever (Box 81, Folder 1641)
- Colombia - Humanities and Arts
  - Escuela Normal Superior; National Library of Bogota (Box 81, Folder 1642)
  - Universidad del Valle (Box 81, Folder 1643)
- Colombia - Social Sciences
  - University of the Andes - Economic Research (Box 81, Folder 1644)
- Colombia - Virus Studies
  - Cali Virus Program (Box 81, Folder 1645)
- Costa Rica
  - Agriculture (Box 81, Folder 1646)
    Aerial views, group portraits.
  - Agriculture - Experiment Stations - Barranca (Box 81, Folder 1647)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, corn.
  - Agriculture - Hacienda Chicua on Volcano Irazu (Box 81, Folder 1648)
    Agriculture, farming, crops, potatoes.
  - Agriculture - Turrialba San Jose (Box 81, Folder 1649)
    Agriculture, laboratories, animals, portraits.
  - Health (Box 81, Folder 1650)
    D. M. Molloy. Public health, children, group portraits, medical exams, sanitation, privies.
  - Fellowships (Box 81, Folder 1651)
    Portraits, Rockefeller Foundation fellowships.
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1652)
    Dr. Louis Schapiro. Diseases, children, case studies, group portraits, dispensaries, houses, families.
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1653)
    Diseases, case studies, children, families, houses, sanitation, privies.
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1654)
    Diseases, group portraits, case studies, children, families, houses, demonstrations, laboratories.
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1655)
    Diseases, case studies, children, families, schools, group portraits, sanitation, privies, laboratories.
  - Hookworm (Box 83, Folder 1656)
    Diseases, demonstrations, health inspectors.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1657)
    Diseases, hookworm, case studies, children, families, houses, sanitation, privies.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1658)
    Diseases, hookworm, group portraits, demonstrations, case studies.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1659)
    Diseases, hookworm, group portraits, demonstrations, houses, sanitation, privies, children, case studies.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1660)
    Diseases, hookworm, sanitation, privies, group portraits, children.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1661)
    Diseases, hookworm, group portraits, dispensaries, children, villages, houses, privies, sanitation.
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1662)
    Diseases, hookworm, case studies, children, families, group portraits, sanitation, privies.
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1663)
    Diseases, drainage ditches, wetlands, group portraits, case studies.
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1664)
    Diseases, sanitation, privies, drainage ditches, group portraits, case studies.
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1665)
    Diseases, drainage ditches, irrigation.
  - Taylor - A Preliminary Survey and Recommendation for Control of Malaria in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1666)
    Diseases, water collection, drainage ditches, wetlands, bridges, irrigation.
  - Public Health Demonstrations (Box 83, Folder 1667)
    Group portraits, demonstrations, parades, children, schools.
  - Development of the "Health Unit Idea" in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1668)
    Nunes. Buildings, laboratories, railroad cars, clinics.
  - Sanitation in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1669)
    Photos showing development of a new type of latrine and the installation of "Planteles Sanitarios" in Santa Ana and Turrialba. Nunes. Sanitation, privies.
  - Health Services (Box 83, Folder 1670)
    Hospitals, clinics, wards, laboratories.
  - Sanitary Engineering (Box 83, Folder 1671)
    Public health, sanitation, sewers, drainage.
  - National Museum - History (Box 84, Folder 1672)
    Museums, exhibits.
  - National Museum - History - Doris Zumari Storm (Box 84, Folder 1673)
    Museums, exhibits, artists.
  - Schools, Libraries, Archives (Box 84, Folder 1674)
  - Fluoroscopy and X-ray (Box 84, Folder 1675)
    Crawford. Diseases, tuberculosis, mobile facilities, medical exams, children.
  - Tuberculosis (Box 84, Folder 1676)
    Cross-reference sheet only. Wells, C. W.
  - Tuberculosis Survey (Box 84, Folder 1677)
    Diseases, families, houses, tenements, children.
- Costa Rica - Fellowships
  - Fellowships (Box 81, Folder 1651)
- Costa Rica - Hookworm
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1652)
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1653)
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1654)
  - Hookworm (Box 82, Folder 1655)
  - Hookworm (Box 83, Folder 1656)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1657)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1658)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1659)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1660)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1661)
  - Schapiro, Louis - Annual Report (Box 83, Folder 1662)
- Costa Rica - Malaria
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1663)
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1664)
  - Malaria (Box 83, Folder 1665)
  - Taylor - A Preliminary Survey and Recommendation for Control of Malaria in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1666)
- Costa Rica - Public Health Demonstrations
  - Public Health Demonstrations (Box 83, Folder 1667)
  - Development of the "Health Unit Idea" in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1668)
  - Sanitation in Costa Rica (Box 83, Folder 1669)
- Costa Rica - Health Services
  - Health Services (Box 83, Folder 1670)
  - Sanitary Engineering (Box 83, Folder 1671)
- Costa Rica - Humanities and Arts
  - National Museum - History (Box 84, Folder 1672)
  - National Museum - History - Doris Zumari Storm (Box 84, Folder 1673)
  - Schools, Libraries, Archives (Box 84, Folder 1674)
- Costa Rica - Tuberculosis
  - Fluoroscopy and X-ray (Box 84, Folder 1675)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 84, Folder 1676)
  - Tuberculosis Survey (Box 84, Folder 1677)
- Cuba
  - Cuba (Box 84, Folder 1678)
    Hospitals, clinics, medical exams, children.
  - Cuban-North American Institute of Culture (Box 84, Folder 1679)
  - Spleen Indices (Box 84, Folder 1680)
    Maps.
  - Medical Sciences (Box 84, Folder 1681)